{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073302163","data":{"timestamp":" 947073302163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" 13bfc3fd-4392-4c3e-8998-10613bcb92cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuvari_voriza-tuvari-jowoma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuvari"," userResponse":" tuvari"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073303304","data":{"timestamp":" 947073303304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" 13bfc3fd-4392-4c3e-8998-10613bcb92cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tuvari_voriza-tuvari-jowoma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073333967","data":{"timestamp":" 947073333966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tunosi_sovipa_voriza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073340576","data":{"timestamp":" 947073340576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_lorewi_veweho_jowoma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073347206","data":{"timestamp":" 947073347206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_veweho_tuvari_dopufa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073354687","data":{"timestamp":" 947073354687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_veweho_tuvari_dopufa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073361329","data":{"timestamp":" 947073361329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sujuye_lununa_veweho"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073367960","data":{"timestamp":" 947073367960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fihulu_yulefo_jowoma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073375428","data":{"timestamp":" 947073375428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fihulu_yulefo_jowoma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073382078","data":{"timestamp":" 947073382078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ravojo_lununa_yujaya"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073389584","data":{"timestamp":" 947073389584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ravojo_lununa_yujaya"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073396239","data":{"timestamp":" 947073396239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pazaba_fihulu_rinoke"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073402905","data":{"timestamp":" 947073402905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ponuvi_bodabi_ravojo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073409554","data":{"timestamp":" 947073409554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_hufuvo_jezipi_fekewa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073417004","data":{"timestamp":" 947073417003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_hufuvo_jezipi_fekewa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073424877","data":{"timestamp":" 947073424877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145432"," gameId":" b80c22ed-4e9f-45d8-941d-cfbef32bc4a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_hufuvo_jezipi_fekewa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}